# Marcelo Vergara

Looking for a software development position. I have worked for 15 years in the information technology area and now I am in between jobs. My experience is mostly in infrastructure and software development support.

GitHub → github.com/marcelorvergara LinkedIn → <u>linkedin.com/in/mvergara/</u>

Site → marcelo-vergara.codes

Rio de Janeiro, RJ – Brazil |Zip.: 21940-400 |+55 21 972 464 530 |+55 21 2466 1955 |marcelorv@gmail.com

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Profarma Retail**, Rio — IT Leader

Apr 2017 - Apr 2019

Administration of on premise and cloud services that run critical business applications (resupply, NF-e, Call Center and TEF). Implementation of new technology and POS applications (ITEC) in all stores. Troubleshooting related to application problems (JAVA, SQL Server and MySQL). Creation of scripts for automation of activities.

## Atos, Rio — Project Manager

Oct 2015 - Sep 2016

Project planning and IT operation support. Support to the technology manager to ensure the correct progress of technological services related to Olympic events. Update and configuration of systems related to event management. Ensuring compliance with SLAs.

# **SICPA**, Rio — Infrastructure Leader

May 2015 - Oct 2015

Acting with corporate areas of Switzerland and Brazil. Project management of technologies implementation.

### **EDUCATION**

### **INFNET**, Rio — B.tech

Oct 2019 - Jun 2022

Already learned about Android (Kotlin), Vue JS, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Agile Software Development, SCRUM, Firebase and SQL.

# UFRJ, Rio —Master's Network

Jan 2006 - Sep 2007

Studies in the areas of computer networks with regard to applications, performance, connectivity, troubleshooting and monitoring.

# **PUC,** Rio — *Programming with New Technologies*

Jan 2002 - Apr 2003

Programming algorithms and data structures, ASP, Java, Oracle, SQL, Linux, VB 6, Delphi and Object Oriented Programming.

#### **SKILLS**

Problem solving, logical thinking, testing and debugging. Fast learning, self-taught and teamwork.

### **COURSES**

Salesforce developer, Javascript, Node.js, Android (Kotlin), Bootstrap, Docker, Java Hibernate, ECMAScript 6 ES 6, Kubernetes, NetBeans, Vuex, Java Swing, Version Control with Git, Responsive Layout, Product Owner.

### **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese and English.

### **CURIOSITIES**

I have made a twitter bot and run them for fun:

@OFlamengoFacts